\_agree Hashing Ad Space I Privacy Policy                     

Privacy Policy​
===============

### 1\. INTRODUCTION

Thank you for your interest in Hashing Ad Space and its products. We are committed to respecting your privacy and personal data and to protecting them. The current privacy policy outlines the ways in which we protect the personal data we collect following your use of our services.

### 2\. IMPORTANT INFORMATION

The goal of this privacy policy is to inform you on how Hashing Ad Space collects and processes your personal data as you use our services. Our website is intended only for persons of over 18 years old (or other age of legal consent, in applicable jurisdictions). It is important that you read this privacy policy together with any other privacy policy or fair processing policy we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy policy supplements other notices and privacy policies and is not intended to override them.

Hashing Ad Space is responsible for your personal data and its controller. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact [admin@hashingadspace.com](mailto:admin@hashingadspace.com). We take your privacy very seriously and are always interested in hearing your concerns.

In order to have a good working relationship, it's very important that the personal data you supply to us is accurate and up-to-date. This is why we ask you to update any personal data you supply to us in order to match your current situation.

Our website may feature links or ads to other websites, plugins, and/or applications. Hashing Ad Space is not responsible for the way those connections collect and/or share your personal data. We strongly encourage you to read the privacy policy for every new website you visit.

### 3\. PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT

We define personal data as any information about an individual which can be used to identify them. Personal data does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data). The types of data we may collect, make use of, store and/or transfer can be grouped in the following categories:

* Identity Data - first name, maiden name, last name, username, marital status, title, date of birth and gender
* Contact Data - billing address, delivery address, email address and telephone numbers
* Transaction Data - details about payments to and from you and other details of products and/or services purchased from us.
* Profile Data - username and password, purchases or orders you made, interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses.
* Technical Data - IP address, login data, browser type and version, time zone setting, location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, and/or other technology on the devices you use to access this website.
* Marketing and Communications Data - preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and communication preferences.
* Usage Data - information about how you use our website, products and services.

Hashing Ad Space may also collect, use and/or share Aggregated Data. Aggregated Data is derived from your personal data and used for strictly statistical purposes. By law, Aggregated Data is not considered personal data because it has been scrubbed of any information that can be used to identify you. Aggregated Data helps us streamline our internal processes, by allowing us to know, for example, how many users in a certain country use one of our services. We would then use this Aggregated Data to offer better services to those particular clients. In situations where Aggregated Data would be combined with your personal information in such a manner where it can be used to directly or indirectly identify you, we would treat the resulting data as personal data and subject it to our privacy procedures.

Hashing Ad Space does not collect Special Categories or Personal Data (details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health, and genetic and biometric data), nor does it collect information about criminal convictions and offences.

In cases where Hashing Ad Space is forced by law to collect personal data and you fail to provide us with it, we reserve the right to cancel any existing or future contract with you until the legal requirements have been met.

### 4\. WAYS WE COLLECT PERSONAL DATA

We collect your personal data through your personal interaction with our website ie: when you create an account and start trading with it. The data we collect can be data that is voluntarily submitted by you (name, address, email address) or data that is collected automatically by our systems (IP address, operating system and version, browser data and version). This data is collected for the sole purpose of creating a better user experience for you.

### 5\. WAYS WE USE PERSONAL DATA

We only process your data within the current legal framework. In most situations, we will process your personal data when we need to sign a contract with you, when we need to comply with a legal obligation or when we will ask for your consent for forwarding your personal data to Hashing Ad Space third party partners for marketing and promotional offers. Hashing Ad Space will always ask for your consent when forwarding your personal data to third parties. You have the right to withdraw this consent at any time by contacting us.

If we ever need to use your personal data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so. Please note that we may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent in compliance with the above rules and where this is required or permitted by law.

### 6\. COOKIE POLICY

Our site uses cookies to share data between all of our services and between our services and our third-party partners. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may become inaccessible or not function properly.

### 7\. PERSONAL DATA DISCLOSURES

Hashing Ad Space may share your personal data with third parties (our marketing partners and law enforcement entities, when required).

Hashing Ad Space requires all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

### 8\. DATA SECURITY

Hashing Ad Space has put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality. We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

### 9\. DATA RETENTION

For tax purposes, Hashing Ad Space is legally obliged to retain basic information about its customers (including Contact, Identity, Financial and Transaction Data) for six years after they cease being customers.  In some circumstances we will anonymise your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes, in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

### 10\. YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS

Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data. These rights are as follows :

rn

rn1. Right to request access to your personal data
rn2. Right to request corrections of your personal data
rn3. Right to request erasure of your personal data
rn4. Right to object to processing of your personal data
rn5. Right to request restriction of processing on your data
rn6. Right to request transfer of your personal data
rn

rn

Should you choose to exercise any of these rights, please contact us and we will analyse your request. You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we could refuse to comply with your request. In that case, we will inform you of our reasons to do so.

9101 LBJ Freeway #300  
Dallas, TX 75243  
support@hashingadspace.com

##### LEARN

##### LEGAL

##### CONTACT

* [Report a bug](javascript:void(0);)

##### SOCIAL

##### SERVICES

* [Affiliates](javascript:void(0);)
* [Partnerships](javascript:void(0);)

##### ASIMI

* [List Asimi](javascript:void(0);)
* [Asimi for business](javascript:void(0);)

##### EXCHANGES

[](javascript:void(0);)

✕

#### Affiliates

### Earn commissions sharing Hashing Ad Space with your friends!

We offer the best affiliate referral program online.

Invite friends to Hashing Ad Space and earn commissions as they earn!  
As your referrals earn watching ads, you earn 10% of what they earn too! talk about a win-win!

On top of that, recommend our advertising products to your friends and earn up to 50% direct commissions!

Watch the overview video below.

✕

#### Report a bug

### If you find an issue with Hashing Ad Space, you may be eligible for a reward!

The team at HashingAdSpace takes all due diligence to make sure our systems are always operating at the highest possible efficiency with up-to-date security measures for our website and members.

In the event you discover something unexpected, a potential security risk, or our systems are not operating as they should, we encourage you to inform us of any issues found.

We offer a minimum 100 Asimi tokens for general system issues and 200 - 3000 Asimi tokens for security related issues.

The bug bounty is determined depending on the severity of the bug reported.

No bounty is paid for reporting general service outages, we are aware of those issues and will resolve them should they occur.

✕

#### Games

### Asimi Earning Games Apps

Launching in Q1 2021, get ready to play multiplayer games on your phone to earn Asimi tokens! Keep an eye on email updates and the [roadmap](https://hashingadspace.nolt.io/roadmap) for launch details.

The gaming industry is thriving, if you are a developer with experience in game building and believe your new game might benefit from Asimi tokens Integration, [contact us](https://hashingadspace.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/requests/new) to open a discussion.

✕

#### Strategic partnerships

### Mutually beneficial partnership offer

Hashing Ad Space is always interested in mutually beneficial partnerships to grow and expand.  
If you believe you have something to offer Hashing Ad Space, in return we can offer you for exposure or other benefits to help you grow your brand. Reach out to us with your proposal.

Advertising:  
We offer strategic partnerships to other advertising services for exchanged advertising impressions and exposure.

Developing:  
We offer support and exposure to new business startups that focus on using Asimi tokens within their business model.

Exchanges/Crypto sites:  
We offer ongoing exposure and direct promotion of exchanges or other crypto-related services that list and share informative articles on Asimi tokens.

Depending on your offer, we can offer you, direct advertising exposure. backlinking for SEO strength, Asimi tokens benefits mentions in our newsletters and more.

✕

#### List Asimi

### Listing Asimi with your service.

If you are interested in listing Asimi with your exchange or crypto related service, please contact us for details.

✕

#### Asimi for business

### Offer/accept Asimi with your business.

If you are interested in listing Asimi with your business, please contact us for details on how we can assist you.

##### Report

×

#### Do you find this ad to be inappropriate?

Please describe why you would like to report this advertisement.. The advertisement is not displaying correctly. This advertisement offends me. This advertisement is a Scam My computer says this site contains a virus

[Yes](javascript:void(0);) NO

##### Report

×

##### Report

×

#### "You already reported."

##### Report

×

#### Do you find this ad to be inappropriate?

Please describe why you would like to report this advertisement.. The advertisement is not displaying correctly. This advertisement offends me. This advertisement is a Scam My computer says this site contains a virus

[Yes](javascript:void(0);) NO
